杰夫  新的课表你看都不看一眼
Jeff, you haven't even looked at the new course catalog.
我都像掉进糖果店的小盆友眼花缭乱了
I'm like a kid in a candy store.
糖果对我这种卖糖的就没吸引力了
Well, the candy has lost its appeal now that I work at the store.
可以说  在这当老师糖多得能让我患糖尿病
You might say becoming a teacher here gave me diabetes.
我刚想说诶
I was just saying that.
你是不是总觉得口渴  疲乏
Are you always thirsty and fatigued
视线模糊  伤口难愈合
and you have blurry vision and your cuts heal slower?
你说的那些都是真的糖尿病临床症状
Those are actual diabetes symptoms.
医生就是这么说的
That's what the doctor said.
所以他有在治疗吗
So, is he treating it?
我问了他一模一样的事
I asked him the same thing.
他怎么说的
What did he say?
他说请在上班时间
He said, make an appointment
通过他的办公室进行约诊
through his office during business hours.
这里是他家  他娃都睡这儿
This is his home, his children sleep here.
医生嘛  你们懂的
You know doctors.
我的天  亲们
Oh, my Gosh, you guys.
这里有一门课程叫「初级欺诈」
There's a class called Basic Grifting.
我们要不要学着团伙作案呀
Should we all learn how to be grifters together?
等等  欺诈师是干嘛的来着
Wait, what do grifters do again?
我来解释
I got this.
-我要你给我五块钱  -不给
- I'll tell you for five bucks. - No.
-帮我报个名  -我也要
- You better sign me up. - Me too.
我一直想学学欺诈
I've always wanted to learn more about grifting
因为看了1990年版  约翰·库萨克和
ever since I saw 1990's, The Grifters,
安杰丽卡·休斯顿演的「骗子」
featuring John Cusack, Anjelica Huston,
而且里面几乎没用到欺诈
and almost no grifting.
大家千万别上欺诈课
You guys, don't take a grifting class.
你们最终只会被欺诈
You're going to get grifted.
就算你选修个海洋学的课
Even more so than by that oceanography class,
你们也连条金鱼也钓不到
only none of you will even get a goldfish,
然后你们又会跑过来跟我哭
then you're gonna come crying back to me.
为什么找你哭
Why you?
因为...承认吧
Because, lets face it,
我是全校最像
I'm the closest thing that Greendale has
老奸巨猾玩欺诈的人
to an experienced grifter.
嗷  所以杰夫是对这种白目事情
Oh, this is one of those things
表示羡慕嫉妒恨呢
where Jeff gets jealous of something dumb.
杰夫吃欺诈师的醋
Jeff's jealous of a grifter.
因为他还想当欺诈师
Because he wishes he was still a grifter
这种事我都能嘲笑你  我还住在房车里哟
That's something even I could mock, and I live in an RV.
我就鄙视你  我的餐桌还是从墙上折下来的
I'm judging you, and my dinner table folds down from a wall.
要我说咱就一起选这门课
I say we all take the grifting class together,
好好玩一把  给杰夫好看
have a great time, and rub it in Jeff's face!
谁来  顺便借我点儿钱
Who's in, and can you cover me?
我会还给你们哒
I'll pay you back.
那我就找你爸妈要钱去
I'll get it from your parents.
我会自己还你钱哒
I'll pay you back.
到时我就去把钱还给你爸妈
At which point I'll pay back your parents.
永远不可能哒
Which will be never.
击掌这事还是留着给你爸妈吧
I'll get a high five from your parents.
好了  每位学生要带上公文箱
All right, each student should bring a briefcase.
人家没有公文箱
I don't have a briefcase.
要不我们带着公文箱欺诈
We're gonna grift with briefcases?
基础个鬼啦  这是高级啊
Basic my ass, that's advanced.
对头
Mm-hm.
我还有多余的几个公文箱
I have a few extra briefcases.
-好震惊哟  -是正规的那种吗
- Shocker. - Are they regulation?
我们每个人都要一个正规的欺诈箱
We each need a regulation grifting briefcase.
这就是在诈你钱了
It's a grift.
什么叫「正规的欺诈箱」
What's a regulation briefcase?
我也不知道啊
I don't know.
不过他们才卖150美元一个
But they're provided for only $150.
你们已经在被诈钱了
You're being grifted.
杰夫你闭嘴
Shut up, Jeff.
你真的是太负能量了
You're such a negative person.
你除了反对还对我们小组贡献了什么
What do you contribute to this group besides negativity?
小伙伴们  看好了  能借我150块钱吗
Guys, watch this, can I borrow $150?
-不借  -就说吧
- No. - See!
现在谁要和我一起来让这货瞧瞧我们的厉害
Now who's gonna come with me and show this guy what's up?
■
本字幕首发于字幕组网站
www.ZiMuZu.tv 欢迎交流
-我会还钱哒  -我会跟你父母要的哒
- I'll pay you back. - I'll get it from your parents.
告诉他们我不稀罕他们的臭钱  谢谢
Tell them I spit on their wealth and thank you.
翻  译    DayDay站在诈骗101教室等大菜
翻  译    蓬蓬裙在绿苑校门口泪眼盼大菜
翻  译    夕橙在幻梦空间暴走哭嚎呼唤大菜
时 间 轴    姜姜表示大菜是谁我不知道←  ←
后  期    鱼骨头问大菜去哪儿浪了
顾 问   greydale
校对/总监  别扭大菜你看这集都什么鬼！
废柴联盟
第六季  第九集
初级欺诈
早安
Good morning.
我是罗杰·迭沙沃教授
My name is Professor Roger DeSalvo,
目前叫这名字
for the time being.
我用过很多假名
For I use many a pseudonym,
比如杰夫·牛肉炖菜  菲利普·开关
such as Jeff Goulash, Philip Switch,
或者巴兹·墙坚
or Baz Ravish.
因为我就是欺诈师
For I am a grifter
这是初级欺诈课
and this is Grifting 101.
你们谁觉得我是故意弄掉的吗
Now which one of you thinks I did that on purpose?
没错  你们以为我失手了
Exactly, you think you've seen me fail.
你们以为自己看到了我的弱点
You think you've spotted a weakness.
我这么跟你们说吧
Let me tell you something,
手腕这么一用劲  我就可以给你
with a flick of a wrist, I could show you a fool
表演一分钟的傻子  或者不止一分钟
one minute, or longer.
我看到你们都带公文箱来了
I see you've got your briefcases.
很不错  都立起来
Excellent. Hold them aloft.
互相传一下
Pass them to each other.
再传回去
Now pass them back.
加速
Do it at speed.
再快
Quicker!
往死里加快
Pass them like hell.
再不快点传你妹就死啦
Pass them like your sister's dying,
继续这样的动作40分钟
and continue that for about 40 minutes.
什么  传40分钟
Wait, 40 minutes?
你叫什么呀小可爱
What's your name, my love?
安妮·埃迪生
Annie Edison.
你怎么说真名
That sounds like a real name,
不是欺诈师名  所以你不是欺诈课老师
not the name of a grifter and therefore, not a teacher.
-干嘛  -我叫灵活·口袋·塔克
- What?  - My name is Slick Pockets Tucker.
你才不叫这名字
No, it's not.
你说对了  我刚才正在想
That's correct. I was just wondering
下节课上什么内容
what the next lesson will be.
下节课就是传两个箱子
The next lesson will be passing two briefcases.
你应该先把传一个箱子做到大师级
You need to master the art of passing one,
然后你才能买另一个箱子
and then you can purchase another briefcase.
-什么  -你话太多了
- What? - You talk too much.
继续传你的
Keep passing.
这本书好好笑
It's a very funny book.
不是吧  欺诈师们
Oh no, grifters.
我得看好我的炸薯条...变成假的了
I better watch my french fries unless, counterfeit?
你们从哪里学来的
Where'd you learn to do that?
我们啥也没学到
We didn't learn anything.
-那门课  -本身就是诈骗
- That class is... - A rip off?
嗯  应该怎么形容呢
Hm, what's another word for that?
他一节课就在那里扔帽子  让我们传公文箱
All he did was throw his hat and make us pass briefcases.
而且他还总向我们卖东西
And, he kept trying to sell us stuff.
欺诈师专用换公文箱的滑石粉
Briefcase swapping talcum for grifters palm,
悄无声息偷天换日公文箱链条油
briefcase hinge oil for silence switcheroos,
还有一种叫「超可信」的袜子
and something called extra believable socks.
袜子打半价买到的  我觉得我有诈到他
Those are actually half off, I kind of feel like I grifted him.
在某种意义上
So in a sense, what happened is
你们上了一堂教欺诈的课
you took a class about grifting.
然...后...
Aaaaaannnnnd
杰夫你就非逼着我们说出来吗
Jeff, you really need us to say it?
-你说... -等等  好吧
- You were - Eh, whoa, whoa, yeah
我非要你们说出来
I need you to say it.
我坐好了你们再说
Let me just get settled.
好了  说吧
Okay go.
你说的是对的
You were right.
太爽了
Yeah.
吃一堑长一智啊亲们
Well, you live and you learn, guys.
总之你们还是吃了一堑
Well, you live anyway.
那现在你愿意帮我们吗
So now, will you please help us?
帮你们啥
Help you?
我们要报复
We want revenge.
我们要把他诈回来
We wanna grift him back.
你们想欺诈一个欺诈师吗
You wanna grift a grifter?
就跟去上这门课一样蠢
That's as dumb as taking his class.
别再送钱就万事大吉了
Just cut your losses.
可是杰夫
But, Jeff.
我原本求着你们别走这条路  你们还嘲笑我
I begged you not to go down this path, and you made fun of me.
你们指着我的脸嘲笑我
You pointed in my face and laughed.
伤着你的感情了真的很对不起
We're sorry we hurt your feelings.
我的感情还好
My feelings are fine.
我只是很懒  而且你们给了我懒的借口
I'm just very lazy, and you gave me an excuse to do nothing.
我才不要因为他变得不懒呢
I'm not just gonna throw that away.
你不想拿下这家伙吗
You don't want to take this guy down?
他比你还懒呢
He's even lazier than you.
对于你这种懒货  他的存在不算一种挑战吗
Doesn't your species consider that a challenge?
你就不想来个非无聊比赛什么的
Shouldn't you be on some kind of reverse pissing contest
直译为逆向尿尿比赛
来较量出谁才是懒中之王吗
to determine who's laziest?
等等  所以你是用那个再吸回到...
Wait, is that where you suck it back up in your...?
不好意思  我以前只用另外的方式做过
I'm sorry, I've only ever done it the other way.
你是说尿尿吗
You mean peeing?
不是  我是说后面的
No, I mean in the back.
他什么也没对我做过
He hasn't done anything to me.
其实  他听起来还蛮牛逼的
In fact, he sounds like a pretty good guy.
我觉得我俩会惺惺相惜
I bet we'd get along.
好节目啊
Good show.
干得漂亮
什么节目
What show?
我没看过
I haven't seen that show.
好吧  祝一切安好
All right.  All the best.
你哪位
And, you are?
本人是这瓶威士忌酒的主人
Well, I was the guy with a full bottle of scotch
且本人对外国人的包容力极高
and a high tolerance for foreigners.
真强大
How robust.
那你就是杰夫·翁格
I'd imagine that you're Jeff Winger.
想不到我们成同事了
Turns out we're going to be office buddies.
先生您好
Hello there, sir.
我叫罗杰·迭沙沃
My name is Roger DeSalvo.
你猜呢
Or is it?
-我碰巧来教授  -初级欺诈
- You see, I happen to be in the... - Grifting 101.
是的  我听说过你
Yes, I've heard about you.
那就是你的办公桌吧
That would be your desk.
如果你要个帮助记忆的方法
If you need a mnemonic device,
那张没别人东西的桌子就是你的
it's the one without someone else's stuff all over it.
技艺高超  手段高明
Well played, very well played.
我必须说
I gotta say.
我很敬佩你的风格
I admire your style.
用给别人上欺诈课的方法欺诈
Grifting people by selling them grifting lessons?
真有才  不过这招我用过了
It's genius, but I called it.
我从来没说我的课是欺诈
I never said my class was a grift.
你别怕我呀  我跟你是一类的
I don't worry about me, I'm one of you.
-以前是一类的  -说说看
- Was, anyway. - Do tell.
以前我在一个顶级律所上过班
Well, I worked at one of the top law firms
在市里面当过律师  后来你猜怎么着了
in the city as a lawyer, but guess what.
我根本不是律师
I'm not a lawyer.
你说的不过是蒙骗说谎
Well, I think you're talking about lying.
然而欺诈应该是一种艺术形式
Grifting happens to be an art form.
谎话的艺术吧
The art of lying.
别说得太装逼
Let's not get high-handed.
欺诈就是说谎
Grifting is lying.
这么说吧  毛线就等于毛衣吗
Okay. So, like a string is a sweater?
油画就等于西斯廷教堂吗
Like, paint is the Sistine Chapel?
当然啦  欺诈包含说谎
Sure, grifting includes lying,
但只有骗子才将欺诈称为说谎
but only a liar would call grifting lying.
也只有妄想的无业游民会美化偷盗
And, only a delusional hobo would glorify stealing.
是吗  你说的貌似不对吧
Really? Did you say something that wasn't true there?
我们可以打个电话问问博物馆
Maybe we should phone the museum.
我以前跟你是一路的  你个混蛋
I was on your side. You're an ass.
你只不过是个没技巧不艺术的暴徒
Well, you're a craftless, artless thug.
我却是上帝的画笔
And, I'm God's paintbrush.
不对  我就是上帝  所以我就比较厉害
No, I am God, which pretty much makes me better than you.
你知道吗
You know what?
我们留同存异吧
Let's agree to disagree.
这才不是重点
It's not important.
好吧
Oh, okay.
所以你也可以说谎嘛
So, you can lie.
你个骗子  哼
Yeah, you liar. Yeah.
我想跟你说话  狗崽子
I wanna speak to you, you son of a bitch.
怎么了
What?
我爱你
I love you.
我也是
I do too.
那就好
Good.
你们干嘛还在做这个
Why are you guys still doing that?
这个是家庭作业
Well, it was homework,
我们越练越好了有木有
and we're getting better, right?
或者说是我们手上的摩擦力
Or, the friction has gradually melted
越来越小了
the handle to fit into our palms.
这种东西练不出什么的
There's nothing to get better at.
这堂课就是欺诈
The class is a grift.
下一个说出欺诈这个词的人就是在...欺诈
The next person who says grift is gonna grift!
天哪  这个词根本无法替代
My God, now it's replacing other words.
好  我要加入你们
All right, I'm in.
我们一起去诈那个狗崽子
Let's grift the son of a bitch.
好耶
Yay!
你们庆祝个啥
Why are you cheering?
他可能说的是别的事呢
He could be saying anything.
欺诈  欺诈
Grift! Grift!
设局
做得好  我不记得你叫什么了
Good work, I can't remember your name.
最新美剧下载
www.ZiMuZu.tv
你也是  我也不记得你的名字了
Likewise, no idea what your name is.
干得好
Great job.
好
All right.
我看你们很快就可以传递
I say you're pretty close to swapping the briefcases loaded with
装满假钱的公文箱了
actual fake money such as this.
这不是真钱  只是报纸剪出来的
This isn't real money, it's just cut up newspaper.
但重量是一样的  一张成本5块
But it weighs the same, costs five dollars a piece.
卖给你们得10快
You'll be using ten.
埃尔罗伊·珀塔斯奈克的电报
Telegram for Elroy Patashnik.
我就是
I'm Patashnik.
您的电报  先生
Telegram, sir.
天啊
Oh, my God.
我的芭芭婶婶在非洲度假的时候死了
My Aunt Baba died on vacation while in Africa.
但她给我留了一百万
But she left me a million dollars,
但非洲政府想要把这笔钱抢走
but the African government wants to seize the funds.
下课
Class dismissed.
你别走
Not you.
你疯了吗
Are you out of your mind?
-什么  -非洲电报
- What? - The African telegram.
像吉姆·贝鲁什一样糟烂的骗局
The Jim Belushi of grift?
著名喜剧演员
你是想骗到我吗
Are you trying to grift me?
我可以分你一万四
I'll cut you in for fourteen grand.
滚
Get out.
快滚
Out.
还有
One more thing.
双重局  好机智
Nice try twice.
-双重局  -诈中带诈
- Twice? - The fake grift within the grift,
或者说是  双诱饵
or the double bean, if you like.
我说一个名字
I'm gonna mention a name
无论你什么反应  我都能看出真相
and however you react, I'll know the truth.
杰夫·翁格
Jeff Winger.
就是他
That's the one!
杰夫·翁格  谁啊
Jeff Winger? What with the, who?
就是他
That's the one.
现在走吧
Out you go.
替我向他问好
Say hi to him.
顺便一提  杰夫·翁格
By the way, Jeff Winger,
三重局真机智
nice try thrice.
欺诈课上得如何
Hey, how was grifting class?
有没有教一些
Did you teach some advanced
只有你懂的高级欺诈技巧
grifting techniques only you could understand?
贝蒂布丁欺诈术
The Brown Betty?
德州油宝宝欺诈术
The Texas oil baby?
著名喜剧演员
反吉姆·加菲根欺诈术
The reverse Jim Gaffigan?
反正我没教非洲电报欺诈术
Well, I wouldn't teach the African telegram.
因为我不是傻子
Since I'm not a hack.
再说现在都是互联网时代了
And also, since the Internet.
好吧  你识破我了
Okay. You got me.
游戏结束  比赛到此为止
Game over. Let's end this competition.
干个杯
Cheers to that.
先生  你的...
Sir, you.
那人把彩票落桌上了
That guy left his lottery ticket on the table.
-那人就是刚才的电报男  -才不是咧
- That was the telegram man. - No, it wasn't.
什么电报
I mean what telegram?
正是  什么电报
Exactly. What telegram?
这年头都互联网时代了  懂吗
Because the Internet, you know?
互联网你知道吗
That place that you obviously went to
你输入「欺诈」进行搜索的互联网
to type in the world grifting.
我会诈到你的
Look, I'm gonna grift you.
会诈得你团团转
I'm gonna grift your ass.
那才是真正的欺诈吗
Or is that the grift?
这哪里是欺诈
None of it is a grift!
都是胡扯淡
It's all nonsense!
好吧  我跟你们说了多少次了
Okay, how many times have I told you people,
教师休息室不是酒吧
the faculty lounge is not a bar?
好了  快走吧
All right, pack it up people.
快点  你们可以不用去教课
Come on, you don't have to go teach a class
但也不能待在这儿
but you can't stay here.
听着  现在停战
Look, truce.
好吗
Okay?
我保证不再诈你了  但你也要保证
Promise no more grifting and promise,
如果中了100万
if this is worth a million,
要和我平分
we'll split it.
你真是个蠢货
You're an idiot.
但也许我是天才呢
Or maybe I'm a genius.
不  我肯定
No, I can answer that.
你绝对是个蠢货
You're definitely an idiot.
蠢货能这样倒着走路  不被撞到吗
Can an idiot walk backwards like this and not hit anything?
-可能吧  -也可能不会吧
- Maybe. - Or, maybe not.
干什么
What?
你来干什么
What are you doing here?
这家伙是个欺诈师
This guy is a grifter.
欺诈课老师
Professor of grifting.
他收了400块  就给了我们两个公文箱
He charges $400, you get two brief cases
还让人家的前男友走火入魔了
and your ex boyfriend becomes an obsessive.
我不知道你和翁格曾是情侣
I didn't know you and Winger were lovers.
如果他想赢得我的尊重  就应该对我坦白的
If he wanted my respect, he should have opened with that.
现在你是在哄我放下戒心吗
Are you trying to be disarming?
还是准备诈得我片甲不留
Are you grifting me out of my arms?
我根本没惹他
I did nothing to that man.
他自称是欺诈师
He called himself a grifter.
我只是纠正了他的说法
I just simply corrected him.
是啊  因为真相对你们俩来说好重要哦
Yeah, because the truth is so important to the both of you.
你要怎样才愿意离开
So what's it gonna cost to make you go away?
怎么样了
Well?
他上钩了
He took the bait.
-棒  -棒
- Yes. - Yes.
等等  我们不是不想让他上钩的吗
Wait, I thought we didn't want him to take the bait?
对  我们的意思是一样的
No, no, we're saying the same thing.
他没上那个我们不想让他上的钩
He didn't take the bait we didn't want taken.
非洲电报
The African Telegram?
对  那是一个假陷阱
Yeah, which was offered as fake bait
就是这个  他没有上钩
and taken as such, ie, not taken.
那会让他觉得一切都在他的掌控中
Because that made him feel in control.
避开了所有可见的陷阱
And by avoiding all visible bait,
他陷入了无形的骗局中
he placed himself on the invisible hook
即担心自己被我们骗而惶惶不可终日
of assuming we're planning to grift him.
-我喜欢  -棒
- Oh, I like it. - Yeah.
但我们确实是要欺诈他  我们心知肚明
But we are. So we knows the truth.
你被欺诈的时候   最不应该知道的事
Isn't that like the one thing you're not supposed to know
不就是这个吗
when you're being grifted?
那个计划他再怎么清楚也没用
He can know a plan all he wants.
但他知道的计划并不是我们的计划
But the plan he knows won't be our plan.
好
Okay.
因为我们的计划是
Because our plan is
不可能被知道的
impossible to know?
因为...
Because...
天啊  这都是杰夫现编出来的
Oh my God, Jeff is making this up as we go.
别吵了
Shh, knock it off.
你们想让我怎么办
What do you want from me?
我们希望你能帮我们诈到他
We wanted you to help us do a grift.
我在琢磨呢
I'm working on it.
即兴发挥吗
Improvisationally?
他的计划肯定是「骗中骗」里的
He definitely had in the plan in The Sting.
如果有人想看的话
If anybody wants to watch it,
提醒一句  本片子需用半天时间观赏
it's important you know, it knocks out half a calendar day.
你们还记得我们在食堂
Look, do you guys remember when we hugged
抱成一团  欢呼雀跃的情景吗
and jumped up and down in the cafeteria?
-记得  -当然
- Yeah. - Obviously.
我们从那以后就没有分开过
Well, having been together virtually non-stop ever since,
你们觉得我拿着一张纸  一只笔
at what point do you think I slipped off with pen and paper
就能策划出一个欺诈大局
and planned an entire grift,
还不被你们知道吗
then withheld it from you?
你啰里吧嗦说了一堆
I guess at any of the several dozen points
普通人只会说一句
when a normal person would say,
我根本没有什么计划
by the way, I have no plan.
「骗中骗」里  两位男主确实相互隐瞒了
In The Sting, they do withhold stuff from each other.
对观众也是  不过我觉得只是为了影片效果
Or from the audience, but I think for effect.
还要提醒一下  这部电影20%是手工绘图
Also, be warned, 20% of the movie is hand drawn.
阿布蒂  你干嘛不娶了「骗中骗」
Abed, why don't you marry The Sting?
好吧  我告诉你
Okay, just so you know,
如果我们真的结了婚  生了孩子
if I do and we have half Sting children,
孩子问我如何欺诈
when they ask me how to grift,
我就告诉他们  看他们妈妈
I'm gonna tell them to watch their mother,
-也别听你的  -对
- not listen to you! - Yeah!
住嘴  行吗
Shut up, okay!
你们这群人  总是挑我的刺
You guys, you're, you're always picking on me, all right?
最近还总是炮轰我
And you've really been hammering me lately.
而我只是想...
All I had was the idea that...
听我说  我需要这个
Look, look, I, I need this.
我得赢过这家伙
I need to be better than this guy.
让我好好想想
So let me think.
-阿布蒂  -在
- Abed.  - Yeah?
电脑带了吗
Did you bring your laptop?
带了  在这儿呢
Yes, right here.
你准备干什么
What do you wanna do with it?
看「骗中骗」
Watch The Sting.
观   看
骗中骗
完了
It's over.
随便吧
Whatever.
谁中枪了
Who got shot?
现在什么情况
What's going on?
斯汀有演这个电影吗[同名歌手]
Was Sting even in it?
这电影真是烂啊
That movie was terrible.
你一直在睡
You slept the whole time.
所以更糟
Yeah, that's worse.
这些对白渗进我的梦里
The dialogue seeped into my dreams.
搞得我的大脑一片无声
My whole brain is long and quiet.
那他们是怎么欺诈他的
So how did they grift him?
简单来说  就是他们造了一座假大楼
Well, they basically made a fake building
又雇了一千个人来配合这场完美骗局
and hired 1,000 people to cooperate in perfect secrecy.
我们也可以吗
Should we just do that?
我们可以再看一部欺诈电影
We could watch another grifter movie.
「火柴人」里的技巧更多
There's more activity in Matchstick Men.
比如呢
Oh, like what?
他们也造了一间假医院
At one point they build a fake hospital.
怎么总是造造造
So much construction!
天啊  好晚了
Oh, God, it's so late.
你们要放弃我了  是吗
You guys are gonna bail on me, aren't you?
我们不得不  杰夫
I think we have to, Jeff.
我们什么办法都试过了
We've tried everything we can.
给我一个周末
Maybe over the weekend
我可以造个假建筑出来
I can make a fake building,
但换公文箱  「骗中骗」什么的
but all the briefcases and the swapping, and The Sting?
我心好累  没法干了
I'm not cut out for it.
我开始觉得
I'm starting to think that
真正的骗局只有电影里才有
real grifts only really happen in the movies,
但即使在电影里  它们也不太说得通
and even in the movies they barely make sense.
我是老年人了
Look, I'm old.
「骗中骗」真的太难看了
The Sting is terrible.
欺诈这事也蠢到家
Grifting is stupid.
这一切都太不好了
The writing's on the wall.
那就这样了吗
So that's it?
这没什么丢人的  杰夫
There's no shame in this, Jeff.
我可说不准
Oh, I don't know about that.
真是一场好戏啊
Well, this is a scene to behold.
跟吉普赛人似的躲在仓库里看「骗中骗」
Holed in the closet watching The Sting like gypsies.
罗杰  我们投降
Roger, we surrender.
你是对的
You were right.
我不是欺诈师
I'm no grifter.
不  我错了
No, I was wrong.
如果你还记得  我称你为暴徒
If you remember, I called you a thug.
暴徒还会奋起抗争呢
Thugs fight.
你更像是...  算了
You're more, nope,
我想不出什么可悲的比喻来形容你了
I can't think of a metaphor pathetic enough to suit you,
杰夫·翁格
Jeff Winger,
不过我想起奥斯卡·王尔德的一句话
though I am reminded of something Oscar Wilde once said
他把羊比作狼
when he compared sheep to wolves.
去你的
Screw it.
你个女人  也敢打我
You hit me with a woman's hand.
你个中西部来的臭婊子
You Midwestern floozy.
人家可是住过纽约的
I lived in New York.
真是够了  他诈我们呢
Yeah, right, he's grifting us.
假血  谁去尝尝
Grift blood. Someone taste it.
肯定是糖浆加食用色素
I'm sure it's Karo Syrup and food dye.
我倒是可以去尝  但我有糖尿病呢
I mean I would, but my diabetes.
清算
19  20  21
19, 20, 21.
你是在数钱的总额  还是在数有几叠钱
Are you counting the amount of money or the number of stacks?
我又要重新数了
I have to start over.
我来吧  你起开
I'll do it, move.
但我想在记录上表明本人
But I want to go on record as being
对这个交易深感厌恶
disgusted by this transaction.
明白  厌恶
Got it. Disgusted.
不好意思  我们直接上法庭不行吗
I, I'm sorry love, but would you rather we took this to court?
不不不  不行
No, no, no, no, no.
如果您愿意私了  我们将无比感激
We appreciate you keeping this between us
而且我还想提醒你
and I do want to remind you
我们这里有很多课程
that we offer a lot of classes
大多数都是只收现金的
and many of them are cash only.
要我在这里上课
Me, take a class here?
敲竹杠呢这是
Talk about a rip-off.
肋骨疼呢这是
Talk about a ribbing.
我都胡言乱语了
What the hell am I doing?
现在记录上有弗兰深表厌恶  还有
You know, so far, Frankie's disgusted and, that's it.
感觉就是对记录的浪费
Seems like a waste of a record.
对不起大家  这都怪我
So sorry guys. This is all my fault.
不怪你  怪我任性斗气
Don't be. I'm the one who got in a pissing match.
-跟一个混蛋  -你才混蛋
- With a jerk. - You're a jerk.
-你混蛋  -你混蛋
- You're a jerk. - You're a jerk.
你们都混蛋
You're all jerks.
这整个学校就是个大废柴之地
And this whole school can suck a big one.
你可以将这句话放到记录里
And you can put that in your record.
对不住各位  因为本人立场不得不记
I'm sorry, guys, I'm bound by my station.
说到犯错这件事  布雷塔
Speaking on that topic, Britta,
鉴于这全是你的错  你被开除了
this is all your fault and you're expelled.
-什么  -不要啊  院长
- What, what? - No, Dean.
别慌  我来搞定
Let, let, let, let, let me handle this.
你不能这么做
No, you can't do that.
布雷塔是我们小组之心啊
Britta's the heart of this group.
她当时创建了这个
She started it as a, as a, as a, as a, as a,
假生物小组  就为了和特洛伊上床
as a fake biology group so that she could have sex with Troy.
-不是啦  -就是这样没错
- No. - That's exactly it.
算了  这事儿我不搞了
Oh, okay. Don't let me handle it.
你不能开除布雷塔  她都在这里上六年学了
No. You can't expel Britta, she's been here six years.
再上三年  她就能拿到两年制学位了
Three more, and she'll have her two-year degree.
布雷塔帮我能够脚踏现实
Britta keeps me grounded in reality.
本季学期还剩四周集数
You can't expel her with four week-episodes
你不能就这么开除她  对不起我又不现实了
left in the season-mester. See, it's starting.
算了  没事的
It's okay, guys. It's okay.
数好了  五万
All right. 50,000.
让我把这个放进去
Whoop, I'll just put this in here.
-给我  -好咧
- Give it to me. - Yep.
谁都别帮我
Don't help me, anyone.
帮我转个身
Turn me around.
回头见
See you later.
计划是咱俩待会再碰头的
The plan was to meet later.
你要怎样才愿意离开
So, what's it gonna cost to make you go away?
其实有一个办法可以让咱们来个痛快
You're know there's a way we could end this very quickly
顺便赚点小钱
and make a bit of money.
我不喜欢这样  你继续讲
I don't like it, but keep talking.
对  原本计划是这样
Yes. That was the plan.
你的计划本是永远不要再出现
And, your plan was probably to never show up.
姑娘好聪明
Clever girl.
不要相信任何人
Don't trust anyone.
等下  刚才你真的有必要打我吗
Hang on. Did you have to hit me, for real?
必要吗  不必要
Have to? No.
现在你被开除了
Now that you're expelled,
不如考虑一下在欺诈界混吧
you might consider a career in grifting.
你在这方面相当有天赋
You're quite good at it.
不知道啊  你们这种人都是怎么过日子的
I don't know. How does one go through life like that?
跟着我  我会告诉你
Well, follow me, and I'll show you.
闭嘴啦你
Oh, shut up.
我答应做这件事只是想让你离开格林德尔
I only agreed to any of this to get you away from Greendale
顺便让杰夫不再烦大家
and out of Jeff's hair.
他是个白痴  我也不愿意看着他
He's an idiot, but I hate watching him
拼了命地跟你斗
spin out trying to beat you.
你个多愁善感的小傻瓜
You sentimental fool.
待会在汽车旅馆做吧
Later at the motel.
汽车旅馆
The motel.
有人说我是幸运的欺诈师
Some say I'm a lucky grifter.
有人说我是王
Some say I'm the King.
他们叫我幸运的欺诈师
They call me the lucky grifter.
他们叫我英格兰之王
They call me the King of England.
我就是王
I am the King.
不是吧
No.
搞什么鬼
What the hell?
闭嘴啦你
Oh, shut up.
我答应做这件事
The only reason I agreed to any of this
只是想让你离开格林德尔
was to get you away from Greendale
顺便让杰夫不再烦大家
and out of Jeff's hair.
什么鬼
What the?
你们俩  给我过来
You two, come back here!
公文箱
Briefcases.
借过借过
Coming right through.
一模一样的公文箱
Identical briefcases.
搞什么  怎么这么多公文箱
What? Why more briefcases?
这根本没意义
This is pointless!
我早就知道她拿走了我的公文箱
I already know she's got my briefcase!
公文箱大游行
Briefcase parade!
你们又是搞哪样
Who the hell are you?
你给我过来
You get back here.
给我过来  把钱还给我
You get back here with my money.
给我过来
Get back here!
罗杰
Oh, Roger.
他们偷走了我的钱
They stole my money.
-啥  -啥
- What? - What?
这些公文箱里有我的钱
Those briefcases contain my money.
他们把我的五万块钱偷走了
They stole $50,000 from me.
五万块啊
50 grand, huh?
你们知道他在讲什么吗
You guys know what he's talking about?
不见得吧  这些公文箱都是我们的
I don't think so. These are our briefcases.
这些都是欺诈课上他卖给我们的学习用具
What is grifting class. He sells these supplies.
150块一个
150 bucks.
真的吗  行啊
Really? Okay.
我们还在坚持换箱子呢
We are still rolling.
而且手法相当娴熟呢
We got pretty good at it, too.
你们看
Check it out.
-抱歉  -不好意思  好
- Ow, sorry. - Sorry. Okay.
罗杰  你干吗带着五万块随处乱走
Roger, why were you walking around with $50,000?
你神经病吧
Are you mental?
注意言辞  朋友
Hey, whoa pal.
这种用词也许在英国很流行  但美国可不行
That usage may fly in the UK, not in the States.
我有个表弟就是精神障碍
I have a mentally challenged cousin.
我妹也有
Sister.
-爆照  我要看照片  -好
- Pics. I wanna see pics. - Okay, you do.
你很清楚你们学校
You know very well that this school
因为我受的这些伤  赔了我五万块
paid me $50,000 in cash for these injuries.
你现在看起来貌似身体蛮好的呀
Well, you seem to be in pretty good shape.
上帝哟  你俩好有爱哦
No, oh, my God! Look at the two of you!
是啊  他就是我做警察的理由
Yeah, he's the reason I became a cop.
你也知道  这世上有很多坏人
You know, a lot of bullies out there.
有无数人目击了我受伤这件事
There are a million witnesses to this.
大家好
Hey, everyone.
大家好  都在餐厅玩儿呢
Hey guys, just hanging out in the cafeteria?
你好  教授  哟  脸怎么了
Hi profess- oh, what happened to your face?
真是难以置信
This is ridiculous.
她好美哦  你俩跟双胞胎一样
She's beautiful. You could be twins.
现在我听到的情况是
So, the statement I'm hearing here is
-你是欺诈课教授  -对
- you're a grifting professor. - Yeah.
你教这些人如何欺诈
You're teaching these people how to grift
但你现在说他们欺诈了你
but you're saying they grifted you.
不是  你个白...我不是这样说的
No, you id. I'm not saying that.
他们才没有诈到我
They didn't grift me.
他们办的这事儿根本算不上欺诈
What they do is not grifting.
他们甚至都不懂这个词是什么意思
They wouldn't even understand what the word meant.
我想大家还是需要认真对待罗杰说的话
I think we need to take what Roger's saying more seriously.
因为听起来
Because it sounds like
他要么是一场粗劣的
he was either the victim of crass,
-毫无艺术感的暴行受害人  -没错
- artless thuggery. - Correct.
也就是说  这里真的有五万块
In which case, there really is $50,000 floating around
是赔给他显而易见的假受伤的
that he was given for clearly fake injuries,
因此现在是他欠学校钱
and that he therefore now owes the school.
啥
What?
或者说迭沙沃教授
Or Professor DeSalvo was targeted
被一群被自己所低估的人盯上
by a group of people
这样一来给他的钱就算是
he vastly underestimated, in which case the money was given
还给学校了  谁也不欠谁
and then taken back and nobody owes anybody anything.
他唯一需要做的就是承认就好了
All he would have to do is admit.
我被欺诈了
I was grifted.
欺诈  欺诈  欺诈  欺诈  欺诈
Grift, grift, grift, grift, grift, grift, grift, grift.
说到底你怎么会在这里
Why are you even here?
谁把你叫来的
Who called you?
没人
Nobody.
我下班后来这里上编织课  他们都知道
I take macrame after work, they know that.
抱歉你被欺诈了
Sorry you got grifted,
如果你想提起诉讼  可以来找我
let me know if you want to press charges and
或者你可以想象一下下场会如何
if you could think of what those would be.
迭沙沃教授  在这种情况下
Professor DeSalvo, under the circumstances
我想你应该会同意你已经不太合适
I'm sure you agree it doesn't makes sense for you
再在这里教课了
to keep teaching this subject here.
是啊  该学的我们都知道了
Yeah, I mean, we kinda know everything there is to know.
你应该把他们的钱全还回去
You should probably refund all their money
我们大家应该都去吃热狗
and we should all go get some hot dogs.
热狗
Hot dogs.
热狗  热狗  热狗
Hot dogs. Hot dogs. Hot dogs.
热狗  热狗  热狗  热狗  热狗
Hot dogs. Hot dogs. Hot dogs. Hot dogs. Hot dogs.
大家全都参与了这件事吗
We were all in it the whole time?
你没有哦
You weren't.
因为我这个人不可信
Because I can't be trusted.
热狗  热狗  热狗
Hot dogs. Hot dogs. Hot dogs.
热狗  热狗  热狗  热狗
Hot dogs. Hot dogs. Hot dogs. Hot dogs.
翁格先生的电报
Telegram for Mr Winger.
你好  里德利
Hey, Ridley.
我把电报员的制服还给院长了
So, I returned the telegram man outfit to the dean.
多谢你了
Thank you so much.
我知道这个星期过得蛮疯狂的
I know how crazy this week's been.
你真的没必要这样做的
You really didn't have to do this.
开什么玩笑  我欠你的
Are you kidding? I owe you.
无论你有什么需要  说一声就好
Whatever you need. Just say the word.
很好  这周末我想请你帮忙搬个床垫
All right. I could use your help moving a mattress this weekend.
行啊
Okay, cool.
-没问题吧  -叫我一声就行
- Is that okay? - Let me know.
我叫瑞恩·里德利
My name is Ryan Ridley.
三年前在健身馆  一个陌生人救了我的命
Three years ago my life was saved by a stranger at my gym.
我感觉欠了他一条命
I felt like I owed him my in life.
很显然他也这样认为
Apparently he agreed.
现在他让我为他做事  我一直在期盼祈祷
Now he has me do things, and I keep hoping and praying
能有一天我会还清恩情  我俩扯平
that one day I'll do enough for him to call us even.
在那之前  我只不过
Until then, I'm just a guy from his gym.
来自杰夫健身馆的
男人
主演
瑞恩·里德利
杰夫·翁格
饰 「他」
■
最新美剧下载请登录字幕组网站
www.ZiMuZu.tv
扫描左边二维码关注我们的微信号
或搜索微信号: ustvboom
非常欢迎爱好者加入字幕组一起翻译海外影视剧
■
你看懂了吗
Did you get any of that?